Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of Research, Vice President for Research Records, 1954-1975 RG.7.A
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1954-1975; 13.8 Cubic feet; (11) cartons, (1) 5" letter document box, (1) 2.5" letter document box
  - Research Activity, 1960-1969; Series 3
    - Geology, Department of, 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - History, Department of, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Home Economics, School of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Industrial Engineering, Department of, 1962, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Medicine, College of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Metallurgy, Department of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Music, School of, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Ophthalmology, Department of, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Polar Studies, Institute of, 1960, 1966-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Political Science, Department of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Sociology, Department of, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Vision, Institute for Research in, 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Zoology and Entomology, Department of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
  - Federal Programs, 1963-1970; Series 4
    - Correspondence: Arthur D. Lynn, Jr. (Associate Dean), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA), undated (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): General Materials (2 folders), 1963-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): State of Ohio Plan for Implementation, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title I -- Project File Summaries, 1963-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title I -- Allied Medical Professions, School of, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title I -- Dental School Addition, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title I -- Humanities Languages Building, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title I -- Mansfield Technical Institute (5 folders), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title II -- General Materials, 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 (HEFA): Title III -- General Materials, 1967, 1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA), undated (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): General Materials, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title I. -- General Materials, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title I. -- Regents Advisory Committee on Continuing Education, General (3 folders), 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title I. -- Regents Advisory Committee on Continuing Education, Projects, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title I (3 folders), 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0010)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title I (3 folders), 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title II -- General Materials, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title II -- Library, General (3 folders), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title II -- Library, Information Science Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title VI -- General Materials, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title VI -- Category I (4 folders), 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1965 (HEFA): Title VI -- Category II, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Mental Retardation, 1966-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) Program, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Public Health Service Act, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
  - Grant Applications, 1962-1969; Series 5
    - Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering (NSF), 1963-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Biochemistry (NSF), 1962 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Botany and Plant Pathology (Rockefeller), 1962-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Chemistry -- Dr. Firestone (AEC), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Chemistry -- Dr. Wolfrom (AEC), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Chemistry -- Pre-Service Teacher Training (NSF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Chemistry -- Renovation of Lab E (OSURF), 1962-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Clinical Psychology (NIH), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Cuban Teachers Project (US Govt.), 1962-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Delinquency Research -- Dr. Reckless (Ford Fdn), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Education, College of (NEW), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Geodesy, Research Center for -- Renovation of, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Geology -- Mass Spectrometer (NSF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Geology -- Mendenhall Renovation (NSF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Geology -- Notre Dame, Joint Effort with University of (NSF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - McPherson Lab -- Renovation of Room 110 (OSURF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Microbiology -- Construction of New Building (NIH), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Nutrition -- Dr. Clements (NSF), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Nutrition -- Institute of Food Technology and (PHS), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Pearce -- Charvat English Project (Research Council), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Physics (NSF), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Physics (AEC), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Stone Laboratory Renovation, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Utley Folklore Project, 1962-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - War Research Building -- Renovation of (OSURF), 1962 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0011)
    - Biomedical Sciences Support Grants -- NIH Documents, 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0012)
    - Research Council (4 folders), 1962-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0012)
    - Research Council (2 folders), 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0013)
    - Research Council: Steering Committee, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0013)
    - Research Council: Urban Task Force, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0013)